ICICI Bank is one of the top private
sector banks in India.  If you are
going to give an interview for a job in ICICI Bank then
this video is going to be very helpful for you.
Because in this video
I will tell you the top six questions
which will definitely be asked to you.
Among these questions, there are some questions
whose answers have neither been given in any other
video before nor have any other
Uber shared with you.  So this
video is going to be very helpful for you.
I will tell you the question in this video.  I will
tell you the reason for asking that question so that you can understand
what strategy you should make for answering.
I will tell you the answer in Hindi if
you have to answer and you will
also get the script of the answer in English word by word at the top of the screen.  So
this video is going to be a one stop solution for you.
You must watch the video from beginning to end.
Start the series of question answers.
Before that I request you that
if you are new to the channel then please
subscribe to the channel.
Like the video and we'll start
with question number one.  The
first question that you will be asked in the ICICI Bank interview is
Tell Me Something About You.  My dear
friend, this question will undoubtedly be asked to you
and by asking this question the
interviewer first wants to make you a little
comfortable and at the same time
he wants to judge how your communication
skills are.  How confident are you and
how prepared have you come for this interview?
And the most important thing the interviewer
wants to know is whether you are suitable for this profile
or not.  So friends, now let us
understand how to answer this question.  The
mistake many people make while answering this question is that they
tell about themselves.
Tell us about your family.  He tells about his education
and his answer ends here.
But you have to start with your name.  You have to
tell your highest qualification.
After that you have to position yourself as to
how you are the best candidate.  Like do
you have skill sets that
make you suitable for a banking job.
How will you answer this?  Sir my name is
Ashish Narang.  I have done B.Com and
during my studies I focused a lot on banking and
finance subjects.
I have also done internships related to customer handling and sales.
I love connecting with people,
solving their problems and helping them
and I
want to grow my career within ICICI Bank.
Its English word by word
version is showing on top of your screen.
If you liked this answer, then please
like the video and definitely subscribe to the channel
because on this channel
we have made a detailed video of answering this question,
which has been
viewed by approximately 2 lakh people till date.
You will find its button on the i button.
You must watch that video also after this video.
Now let us move towards question number two, the
chances of which being asked are not 100 but 101%.
This question is why do you want to
join ICICI Bank?  My dear friend, by
asking this question the interviewer
wants to know whether you are really
serious about the ICICI Bank interview, do you really
want to work here or have you
come randomly for the interview, if you are serious then
you have definitely done research about the bank,
while answering this you have to say that
ICICI Bank is India's leading private
sector bank and it is known for its innovative
products and customer service.
I like ICICI Bank very
much because ICICI Bank holds leadership position not only
in banking services but also in insurance, loans
and digital payments.
I think there are going to be a lot of
opportunities to learn and grow here.
That's why I want to
join ICICI Bank.
You can see the answer to this question word by word at the top of the screen.
You can take a screenshot of this also.  To answer this,
you should know more about ICICI Bank
because
many questions can be asked on its follow up also.
Like what are the products of ICICI Bank
?  When was it established?  How many
branches does the network have?
We have made a dedicated
video answering all these questions.  You can also see that by clicking on the i button.  You
must watch this video if you want to crack the ICIC Bank
interview.  If you have
found some value in the video so far, please don't
forget to like the video.  We move on to the
next question.  The next question is how will you
handle a difficult customer?
Friends, this question will obviously be asked
because banking is a
service business and there are
many customers inside the bank who are often unsatisfied.
Many times they may not have got the information correct.  So
many times they
reach out to the bank employees in anger.
So how will you handle this situation?  This is what the
interviewer wants to know.  Right?  So
what answer do you have to give to this?  First of all, I will
listen to the customer's problem very carefully and calmly.
I will not interrupt him at all while he is speaking.
After understanding the entire problem well, I will suggest them a solution.
I will try my best to solve the problem at my level itself.
If the problem is
not solved then I will
also involve my senior for problem solution.
During this entire process, I will
ensure that the customer feels that we are
genuinely interested in solving his problem and
we want to solve his problem seriously
and
I will maintain his respect throughout the process.  Now
you can see the word by word answer at the
top of the screen.  Now let's move on to the
next question which is
related to sales.  Whether
you go into sales or operations within banking,
you will definitely get some sales targets
and you will have to achieve them.   The
next question is related to this,
which is that there are targets in banking jobs.
So how do you manage the pressure to meet your targets
?  The
reason for asking this question is that the
freshers who come to the bank
leave the job very quickly because
they are not able to handle the pressure.
Achieving targets is a different matter.  But
facing the pressure of targets is a different matter.  Right?  So the
HR of the bank
wants to know this by asking you this question.  The filter wants to see
if you can handle a little pressure
or if you will run away in fear.  Like,
you have to answer this question very smartly.
While answering this, you have to
say that I make my daily and weekly plan so
that there is no rush at the month end.
If the targets seem difficult,
I discuss them with my seniors and team
and try to revise the strategy.
I feel that
working under some pressure
improves our efficiency and we
can get good results.  Make sure to memorize its answer word
by word which is visible to you on the top of the screen
because this question will be
asked to you and if you do
not give a good answer to it then you will not be selected.
Right?  The next question is being
asked a lot these days.  Earlier this
question was asked less but now this
question is being asked a lot.  So
this is the question if you get a lot of multiple tasks within a day.
One problem is
that the customer is unsatisfied.  His
problem has to be solved and the target of second sales has to be
met.  So how do you
handle this situation?  By asking this question,
HR evaluates your time management and
multitasking skills.
So this is how you have to answer smartly.
While answering the question, you will
say that I will first focus on solving high priority and
customer centric problems.
Because I believe
that only highly satisfied customers
give good business in the long term.
After rolling the complaint, I will organize my
sales tasks
well,
prioritize them and
complete them efficiently. I
know very well that
multitasking and proper planning are very
important skills for a banker.  That's why I
focused a lot on developing these skills.
Now its English answer is
visible to you at the top of the screen.  I hope
you found all these question answers very
interesting.  But in this video
we talked about only five questions.
Apart from this, many more
questions can be asked from you in ICICI Bank interview.
So I highly
recommend you to watch this video on
repeat.  You must watch the two videos
I recommended.
You can also purchase our e-book as well.
Inside the e-book we have covered 100
plus bank interview question answers.
We have given to the point and perfect answers.  By preparing for these,
you can easily crack the bank job.
And my dear friend, this is not an e-book worth ₹500 or
₹600.  You will
get this e-book for just ₹99.  Go and purchase it, the
value of the job you are going to start after cracking the interview is many
thousands of times more than ₹99.  So please there
is a link inside the description section.  Go
purchase this e-book right now and
crack your interview.  If this video
helped you in some way or you learned something, then
please like the video, subscribe to the channel
and don't forget to share it with your friends.
Thank you for watching
and before you go, do check out these two videos.